Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boulé; Records apap333
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1984-2021; 2; 3.22 cubic ft.
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Celebration, Beta Psi Boulé, 2014 (Video-tape 2)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Celebration, Beta Psi Boulé, 2014 (Video-tape 2)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Celebration, Beta Psi Boulé Commemorative Pen, 2014 (Artifact-box 2)
    Archon Ray Walker presented each Archon in the Beta Psi Boulé with one of these pens.
  - Dr. Maurice Thornton, 2015 (Flat-file 5)
  - Dr. Maurice Thornton, 2019 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Dr. Maurice Thornton Review of The Butler: a Witness to History, Friends of the Albany Public Library, 2014 (Dvd 6)
  - Times Union Article on Death of Maya Angelou Featuring Dr. Leonard A. Slade, Jr., 2014 (Flat-file 3)
  - Transfers, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Tribute to Virgil Hall Hodges, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Tribute to the Reverend Edward Smart, 2018 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - University at Albany Department of Africana Studies, 2014; 2019; Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - University at Albany Department of Africana Studies Accolades Advertisement Featuring Dr. Leonard Slade, 2013 (Flat-file 4)
  - University at Albany Department of Africana Studies, Commencement Recognition Program, 2014 (Dvd 8)
  - University at Albany President Robert Jones, Capital Region Conversation, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Victory Card for Congressman-Elect Antonio Delgado, 2018 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Youth Development and Creative Leadership Program Handbook, Kappa Boulé, 1989-1991 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
- Special Events, 1985-2018; 3; 1.9 cubic ft.
  The Special Events series contains records of the Biennial Boulé meetings and conferences for the Northeast Region and some of the Grand Boulé conferences attended by members of the Beta Psi Boulé. The bulk of the series consists of files for the 6th - 8th, 13th – 19th, and 22nd Biennial Northeast Regional Conferences from 1985 – 2017, and the Beta Psi Regional Planning Committee's records from planning and facilitating the 15th Biennial Regional Conference held in 2003 in Albany. The series also contains records pertaining to the Northeast Region Executive Committee and its meetings.
  - 6th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 1985 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 1)
  - 7th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 2)
  - 8th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 3)
  - 13th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 4)
  - 14th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2001-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 5-6)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Banquet Event Orders, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 7)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Mailings and Program, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 8)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Memorabilia, 2003; 2011 (Oversized 4)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Name Tags, Ribbons and Registration Signs, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 9)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: News Clipping, 2003 (Oversized 4)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Paid Registration, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 10)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 11)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Report of Officers, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 12)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Reports and Policy Resolution, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 13)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Summary Report, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 14)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Update Presentation Drafts, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 15)
  - 16th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Report of Officers, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 16)
  - 17th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 17)
  - 19th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2011 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 18-19)
  - 22nd Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2017 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 20)
  - Albany Ambassador Award, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 21)
  - Albany County Convention and Visitors Bureau: Conference Planning Guide, 2003-2004 (Cd 3)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees, 2001-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 22-24)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Albany County Convention and Visitors Bureau Binder, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 25)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 26)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Correspondences, 2001-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 27)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Exhibits Committee, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 28)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Hotel Package Offers, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 29-30)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Preliminary Reports to Regional Committee, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 31)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 1984; 1986; 1989-1990; 1992 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 1)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 1992 (Video-tape 1)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 1994; 1996; 2000; 2002; 2010 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 2)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 2016 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 3)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 2018 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 4)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé: Official Photo, 1984 (Flat-file 2)
  - National/Regional Reports, 1982-1983; 1985; 2002-2003; 2005 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 5)
  - Northeast Region Executive Committee, 1985-2009 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 6-7)
  - Northeast Region Leadership Summit, 2018 (Box 2 (3-Special Events))
  - Sigma Pi Phi Grand Officers and Executive Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 9)
- Publications, 1983-2021; 4; 4.0 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically
  The Publications series consists of The Boulé Journal which is a quarterly publication compiled by Sigma Pi Phi's Grand Boulé. It is the fraternity's official publication and subordinate Boulés' submit items for consideration. The publications span from 1983 to 2017 and are almost a complete collection of issues published in those years.
  - The Boulé Journal, 1983 Winter-1984 Spring (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1984 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1985 Spring (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1985 Summer (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Summer (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Winter (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Spring (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Winter (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Spring (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Summer (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Winter (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1989 Spring (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1989 Summer (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1989 Fall (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Spring (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Summer (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Fall (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Winter (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Winter 2 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1991 Spring (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1991 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Summer (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Winter (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Summer (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Winter (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Summer (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Winter (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Spring (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Summer (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Winter (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Spring (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Summer (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Fall (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Winter (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Spring (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Summer (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Winter (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Spring (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Summer (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Fall (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Spring (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Summer (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Fall (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Winter (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Spring (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Summer (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Fall (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Winter (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Spring (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Summer (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Fall (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Winter (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Spring (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Summer (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Fall (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Winter (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Spring (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Summer (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Fall (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Winter (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Summer (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Fall (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Winter (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Spring (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Summer (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Winter (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Summer (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Winter (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Summer (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Fall (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Winter (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Spring (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Summer (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Fall (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Winter (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Spring (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Summer (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Fall (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Winter (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Spring (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Summer (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Fall (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Winter (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Spring (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Summer (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Fall (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Winter (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Spring (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Summer (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Fall (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Winter (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Spring (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Summer (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Fall (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Winter (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Spring (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Summer (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Fall (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Winter (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2015 Spring (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2015 Summer (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2015 Fall (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2015 Winter (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2016 Spring (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2016 Summer (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2016 Fall (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2016 Winter (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2017 Spring (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2017 Summer (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2017 Fall (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2017 Winter (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2018 Spring (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2018 Summer (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2018 Fall (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2018 Winter (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2019 Spring (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2019 Summer (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2019 Fall (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2019 Winter (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2020 Spring (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2020 Summer (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2020 Fall (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2020 Winter (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2021 Spring (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2021 Summer (Box 4, Folder 27)